I'm telling you, if xenon emits ultraviolet light...
Si le xénon émet des ultraviolets,
...those dark-matter discoveries must be wrong.
cette matière noire est fausse.
Yes, well, if we lived in a world where slow-moving xenon produced light...
Si le xénon lent produisait de la lumière,
...then you'd be correct. Also, pigs would fly...
tu aurais raison. Les cochons voleraient,
...my derriere would produce cotton candy...
mon derrière produirait des bonbons
...and The Phantom Menace would be a timeless classic.
et La Menace fantôme serait un classique.
Oh, you're so arrogant.
Tu es si arrogant.
If you were a superhero, your name would be Captain Arrogant.
Tu pourrais être Capitaine Arrogant.
And you know what your superpower would be? Arrogance.
Ton superpouvoir serait l'arrogance.
You're wrong again. If my superpower were arrogance...
Tu as encore tort. Si j‘étais arrogant,
...my name would be Dr. Arroganto.
je serais le Dr Arroganto.
I love watching Raj and Sheldon try to work together, heh.
J‘adore les regarder travailler ensemble.
Yeah. It's like if Alien and Predator decided to go partners in a Jamba Juice.
C‘est comme si Alien et Predator s‘associaient pour ouvrir un bar.
Has it occurred to you you're missing the big picture? If you look--
Est-ce qu‘il t'arrive de te tromper ? Si tu...
-Penny? Penny? -What's up?
- Penny ? - Quoi ?
Nothing. I just wanted to make Raj stop talking.
Rien. Je voulais faire taire Ra].
No, no, no. He won. Suck it up.
Non. Il a gagné. C‘est comme ça.
PENNY: I'd ask if you want dessert...
Aucun dessert, non ?
...but Sheldon doesn't eat dessert on Tuesdays.
Sheldon n'en mange pas les mardis.
If Raj wanted something, he couldn't tell me.
Raj ne peut pas me le dire.
Howard won't order anything, but he'll come up with some comment...
Howard ne va rien prendre mais faire des commentaires
...involving the words "pie" or "cheesecake."
au sujet des tartes.
Leonard's lactose intolerant. He can't eat anything here...
Leonard est allergique. Il ne peut rien avaler
...without his intestines blowing up like a balloon animal.
sans que son intestin ne gonfle comme un ballon.
-Hang on. I could have the fruit platter. -You want the fruit platter?
- Le plateau de fruits. - Tu veux des fruits ?
-Does it have melon? -Yeah.
- Du melon ? -Oui.
No, I can't eat melon.
Je n'en mange pas.
Oh, Howard, heads up. Your ex-girlfriend just came in for her shift.
Howard, regarde. Ton ex Vient d'arriver.
-When was the last time you saw her? -Not since we broke up. Wow.
- La dernière fois que tu l'as vue ? - Lors dela rupture.
How am I gonna play this?
Commentjouer le coup ?
Sophisticated and relaxed? Friendly, noncommittal?
Sophistiqué et détendu ? Amical et évasif ?
Cold and distant?
Froid et distant ?
-Hi, guys. -Hey.
- Salut.
Hello.
Bonjour.
I see you decided to go with pathetic and frightened.
Tu as choisi d'être pathétique et effrayé.
It's one of his best moves.
Sa meilleure tactique.
So, my dear, we meet again.
Alors, on se rencontre à nouveau.
-Hello, Howard. I've missed you. -Heh.
Bonjour, Howard. Tu m'as manqué.
I've missed you, Katee Sackhoff.
Toi aussi, Katee Sackhoff.
-One question. -Anything.
- Une question. - Ce que tu veux.
Why am I wearing my Battlestar Galactica flight suit in bed?
Pourquoi je porte ma tenue de combat dans le lit ?
Why are you in bed with me?
Pourquoi es-tu dans mon lit ?
I mean, if we start to question this, it all falls apart.
Si on commence à poser des questions, tout est fini.
Sorry.
Désolée.
Oh, ravish me, Howard. My loins ache for you.
Fais—moi plaisir. Je brûle de désir pour toi.
Okay, if you insist.
Si tu insistes.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Howard, have you seen my girdle?
- As-tu vu ma gaine ? - Non, maman !
I can't find it, and I'm late for my Weight Watchers meeting!
Je vais être en retard pour ma réunion Weight Watchers.
Maybe it committed suicide! Leave me alone!
Elle s‘est peut-ètre suicidée ! Lâche—moi !
Now, where were we?
Où en étions-nous ?
I believe you were about to rip off my uniform with your teeth.
Tu étais sur le point de m‘enlever cet uniforme.
Bernadette. What are you doing here?
Bernadette. Que fais-tu la ?
Well, ifl had to guess, I'd say I'm here because you saw me this evening...
A mon avis, je suis la car tu m'as vue ce soir
-...and you're still hung up on me. -No, I'm not.
- et que tu tiens à moi. - Non.
KATEE: Clearly you are.
Si.
Otherwise, based on past experience, we'd be done by now.
Vu nos expériences passées, on aurait déjà franchi le cap.
Okay, I'm a little confused here.
Je suis un peu perdu.
Oh, my. Can I help?
Besoin d'aide ?
-Not that kind of confused. -What's George Takei doing here?
- Pas perdu comme ça. - Que fait George Takei ici ?
Howard, do you have latent homosexual tendencies?
Tu as des tendances homosexuelles ?
-Of course not. -So you say, yet here I am.
- Non. - C‘est ce que tu dis.
George, let me ask you something.
Juste une question, George?
How did you deal with being typecast as a science-fiction icon?
Comment vis-tu ton rang d'icône de science—fiction ?
It's difficult. You try and stretch as an actor, do Strindberg, O'Neill...
C‘est dur. Tu essaies de changer et d‘évoluer en tant qu‘acteur,
...but all they want is, "Course laid in, captain."
mais ils veulentjuste voir Sulu.
Tell me about it. It's frakking frustrating.
Comme tu dis, c‘est vraiment frustrant.
Wait, Katee. Why are you leaving?
Attends, Katee. Pourquoi pars-tu ?
She's leaving because you really wanna be with me.
Elle part car tu veux être avec moi.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Howard, I found my girdle! It was in the dryer!
J'ai trouvé ma gaine! Elle était dans Ie sèche-linge.
Great, Ma!
Super!
MRS. WOLOWITZ: I think it shrunk!
Elle a rétréci ! Je suis boudinée comme le bonhomme Michelin!
And with that mental picture, I think we're done for the evening.
Avec cette image, c‘est la fin dela soirée.
You never told me what happened between you and Bernadette.
Que s'est-il passé entre Bernadette et toi ?
-I did a stupid thing, heh. -Yeah, I guessed that.
- J'ai fait un truc stupide. - Je m'en doutais.
It was the kind of thing that makes it kind of hard to face her now, heh.
Une chose qui fait que je ne peux plus la regarder.
That covers anything from farting in bed to killing a homeless guy.
Tu as pété au lit ? Tué un sans-abri ?
Oh, my God, you ran over a hobo.
Mon Dieu, tu as écrasé un clochard.
No. And stop asking.
Non. Et arrête d‘y penser.
Fine. You wanna get back together with her.
Tu veux te remettre avec elle.
You're too ashamed to face her because of whatever it is you did.
Tu as trop honte pour la regarder à cause de tes actes.
-In a nutshell. -Okay, well, how about this?
- En quelque sorte. - Ecoute—ga.
Kidnap Bernadette from the opera wearing a creepy mask...
Kidnappe Bernadette en portant un masque.
...so she doesn't know it's you.
Elle ne te reconnaîtra pas.
Now, you see, I don't know if you're kidding or not.
J'ignore si tu plaisantes ou non.
You're being unreasonable. Why can't I have a desk?
C‘est fou. Pourquoi je ne peux pas avoir un bureau ?
Our collaboration is a work of the mind. We don't need desks.
C‘est un travail mental. Pas besoin de bureau.
-You have a desk. -Correct.
- Tu en as un. - Correct.
-But I can't have one. -You're two for two.
- Et moi, je ne peux pas. - Toutjuste.
-Why can't he have a desk? -Oh, Lord, will this day never end?
- Pourquoi ? - Ce jour ne finira donc jamais ?
As I've explained repeatedly to Dr. Koothrappali...
J'ai déjà expliqué au Dr Koothrappali,
...whose ability to comprehend the American idiom...
qui comprend notre langue
...fails him when it's convenient, there's no money in my budget...
quand ça l'arrange, que mon budget est trop serré
...for additional office furniture.
pour acheter du mobilier.
Oh. But there's money for a drawer full of Red Vines...
Mais tu as assez d'argent pour acheter
...a marshmallow-shooting rifle...
un fusil à guimauve
...and a super-executive ant farm with glow-in-the-dark sand?
et une fourmiliére avec du sable phosphorescent ?
Yes.
Oui.
-What if he buys his own desk? -What if I buy my own desk?
- Et s'il se l'achète ? - Si je me l'achète ?
-That's ridiculous. -Why?
- Ridicule. - Pourquoi ?
Because--
Parce que…
Yes?
Oui ?
--it's my office.
C‘est mon bureau.
-Sheldon. -All right, all right.
- Sheldon. - D‘accord.
-He can buy his own desk. -And I can put it in your office?
- Et le mettre dans ton bureau ?
Well, you really wanna dot the l's...
Tu tiens vraiment à mettre
-...and cross the T's, don't you? -Why would you want...
-les points sur les i ? - Une fourmiliére
-...a glow-in-the-dark ant farm? -They do their best work at night.
- phosphorescente ? - Elles travaillent mieux la nuit.
Ah, it's okay.
C‘est bon.
SHELDON: Penny.
Penny.
Would you have opened the door if you knew it was me?
Tu n'aurais pas ouvert si tu avais su.
Not since I found out the teddy bear you gave me had a webcam in it.
Non, vu que j'ai trouvé une webcam dans ta peluche.
I just have a question. Uh, does Bernadette ever talk about me?
Juste une question : Bernadette t‘a parlé de moi ?
-Yeah. Absolutely. -She does?
- Oui. - Vraiment ?
Yeah, sure. Just yesterday, she asked, "Why is Howard hiding under the table?"
Oui. Elle m‘a dit : ”Pourquoi s'est-il caché sous la table ?"
-She saw that, huh? -Oh, no, not at first.
- Elle m‘a vu ? - Non.
Right after I pointed it out.
Mais je lui ai dit.
Let me ask you something else. Is she seeing anybody?
Autre chose : est-ce qu'elle voit quelqu'un ?
Uh, not that I know of.
Pas que je sache.
While we're on the subject, why did you guys break up, anyway?
Tant qu'on y est, pourquoi avez-vous rompu ?
-Oh. I'd rather not say, heh. -Howard, if you want my help...
- Je ne veux rien dire. - Pour t'aider,
-...l've gotta know what happened. -lt's embarrassing.
-je dois tout savoir. - C‘est génant.
Yeah, that's what I'm counting on. Spill.
C‘est bien ce que j‘espérais. Alors ?
Okay, well, you know "World of Warcraft"?
Tu connais World of Warcraft ?
The online game? Sure.
Le jeu en ligne ? Oui.
Well, did you know...
Tu sais que les personnages peuvent avoir des relations sexuelles ?
Oh, God. I think I see where this is going.
Mon Dieu, je vois où tu veux en venir.
Her name was Glissinda the Troll.
Elle s‘appelle Glissinda Ie Troll.
Bernadette walked in on me...
Bernadette m‘a surpris
...while we were doing the cyber-nasty under the Bridge of Souls.
quand on faisait des cochonneries virtuelles sous le Pont des Ames.
Oh, you're right. That is so embarrassing.
Tu as raison. C‘est très embarrassant.
-Would you talk to her? -Bernadette or the troll?
- Tu lui parleras ? - A Bernadette ou au troll ?
Bernadette. She was so mad at me, she wouldn't listen to my side of the story.
A Bernadette. Elle n‘a pas écouté mon point de vue.
Well, what was your side?
Qui est ?
For all we know, Glissinda the Troll wasn't even a real woman.
Glissinda Ie Troll n‘est pas une femme réelle.
She could've been a 50-year-old truck driver in New Jersey.
Elle pourrait être un Vieux routier dans le New Jersey.
Really? And that didn't make her feel better?
Vraiment ? Et elle devrait se sentir mieux ?
Will you talk to her?
Tu lui parleras ?
See if there's any chance we could get back together?
Pour voir s'il reste encore un espoir ?
Uh, gee, Howard, I really don't wanna get in the middle of this.
Je ne veux pas me mêler à tout ça
No. Why would you?
Pourquoi le ferais-tu ?
I'm just another lonely nerd living with his mother...
Je ne suis qu'un pauvre intello vivant chez sa mère
...trying to find any scrap of happiness he can.
qui essaie de trouver un peu de bonheur.
Maybe to make up for the fact that his dad left them when he was 11.
Sans oublier l‘abandon de mon père quand j‘avais 11 ans.
Okay, I will think about it.
Je vais y penser.
You know, I've always blamed myself for him leaving.
Je me sens coupable de son départ.
I always thought it was because I wasn't the son he wanted.
Je n'ai jamais été le fils qu'il voulait.
I said I'd think about it.
Je vais y penser.
I wasn't athletic. Yeah, I was kind of sickly--
Je n‘étais pas sportif. J‘étais plutôt...
Okay, fine. Look, look, I'm calling her now. See?
D‘accord. Je l‘appelle immédiatement.
Thank you.
Merci.
Howard asked Penny to talk to Bernadette, and she did.
Howard a demandé à Penny d‘appeler Bernadette.
Bernadette agreed to meet him for a cup of coffee.
Elle a accepté de boire un café avec lui.
-One question. -Yeah?
- Une question. -Oui ?
Why on earth are you telling me all this?
Pourquoi me racontes-tu tout ça ?
I don't know. Sometimes your movements are so lifelike...
Je l‘ignore. Parfois tes gestes sont si normaux
...I forget you're not a real boy.
quej'oublie que tu n'es pas un humain.
You said I could buy a desk.
Tu étais d‘accord.
This isn't a desk. This is a Brobdingnagian monstrosity.
Ce n‘est pas un bureau mais une monstruosité gargantuesque.
Is that the American idiom for "giant, big-ass desk"?
Ça veut dire ”bureau qui déchire tout" ?
It's actually British.
C‘est un mot de Rabelais.
-Can you say it again for me? -Brobdingnagian.
- Répéte-le. - Gargantuesque.
-One more time.
- Encore.
-Now three times fast. -Brobdingnagian. Brobdingna--
- Trois fois de suite. - Gargantuesque. Gargant...
How did you even get it in here?
Comment l‘as-tu fait entrer ?
That's for me, Ramone, Julio, Jesus, and Rodrigo to know...
Un secret entre Ramone, Julio, Jesus, Rodrigo et moi.
...and you to find out.
A toi de le découvrir.
All right, you've made your point.
J'ai compris.
A fine prank. Very amusing. Ha-ha-ha.
Trés bonne blague. Trés amusant.
Now get it out.
Maintenant, fais-Ie sortir.
-No. -Yes.
- Non. -Si.
-No. No. -Yes. Yes.
- Non. Non. -Si. Si.
l have three brothers and two sisters, Sheldon. I can do this all day.
J'ai trois frères et deux sœurs. Je suis incollable.
All right, if you're not going to remove it, I'll remove it for you.
Si tu ne l'enlèves pas, je vais le faire moi—mème.
Knock yourself out.
Je t'en prie.
-Help me move my desk. -No.
- Sors mon bureau. - Non.
-Yes. Yes. -No. No.
-Si. Si. - Non. Non.
It's too Brobdingnagian.
C‘est trop gargantuesque.
Why do you even want this here?
Pourquoi fais-tu ça ?
Its size is completely disproportionate to its purpose.
Sa taille est disproportionnée par rapport au but.
Well, seeing as its purpose was to piss you off, I'd say it's spot-on.
Le but étant de te casser les pieds, il est parfait.
All right, I see what's going on.
Je comprends.
This is the opening salvo in what will be an escalating series...
C‘est la première salve d‘une série intense
...ofjuvenile tit-for-tat exchanges. Well titted.
de coups prêtés pour coups rendus. Joli coup.
-Thank you. -Stand by for my upcoming tat.
- Merci. - Attends de voir le mien.
-Hey, Sheldon? -Yes?
- Hé, Sheldon ? - Oui.
See what I did there? I turned it around.
Renversement de situation.
-Sorry. I had to clock out. -Oh, no, that's okay. Ahem.
- Désolée. Je devais pointer. - Ce n‘est rien.
-How have you been? -Okay. You know, busy. School, work.
- Comment vas-tu ? - Trés occupée. Études, travail.
-You? -Same.
- Et toi ? - Pareil.
I took a scuba-diving course over the summer...
J'ai pris des cours de plongée
...but it turns out I'm terrified of the ocean.
mais je suis terrifié par l'océan.
That's too bad.
C‘est dommage.
You wouldn't know anybody who wants to buy a wet suit? Boys' large.
Tu connais quelqu'un qui voudrait acheter une combinaison ?
Yeah, forget it. Not important.
Oublie—ça. Ce n‘est pas important. Tu vois quelqu'un ?
-To be honest-- -Hey, how are we doing over here?
- Pour être honnête... - Ça va ici ?
-Can I get you something to drink? -Uh, not for me.
- Vous voulez à boire ? - Pas moi.
-l'm okay. -Are you gonna order food?
- Ça va. - Vous mangez ?
-Maybe later. -Okay.
- Plus tard. - D‘accord.
-So are you seeing anybody? -No.
- Tu vois quelqu'un ? - Non.
That's what I told him when he asked me. I hope that's not out of line.
C‘est ce que je lui ai dit. Tu ne m'en veux pas, j'espère ?
-No, it's fine. -Heh, Penny, can we have a little privacy?
- Non. C‘est bon. - Tu nous laisses un peu ?
-Oh, heh, I'm sorry. -Heh.
Je suis désolée.
What about you? Have you been seeing anybody?
Et toi ? Tu fréquentes quelqu'un ?
Well, I mean, you know how it is with guys. We have needs, and-- Heh.
Tu connais les hommes. On a des besoins...
-So you've been seeing other girls? -Well, uh, not real girls.
- Tu as vu d'autres filles ? - Pas des filles réelles.
Does that mean slutty trolls?
Ces créatures dévergondées ?
You look thirsty. I brought you some iced tea.
Vous avez l‘air d‘avoir soif. Tenez.
-Thank you. -lt's passion fruit. New on the menu.
- Merci. - Aux fruits dela passion.
-I know. I work here. PENNY: Oh.
Je sais. Je travaille ici.
Yeah, you're right. Doy. So, Howard, trolls, yay or nay?
C‘est vrai. Alors, les trolls : pour ou contre ?
Okay, fine. Look, I'll admit, heh...
D‘accord. Je reconnais
...there are dark, sordid little corners of the Internet...
qu'lnternet a des recoins sordides et obscures
...where the name Wolowizard is whispered in hushed tones.
où mon nom, Wolowizard, est prononcé à voix basse.
But the only reason I go there, the only reason I've ever gone there...
Si je vais dans ces coins, c‘est parce que
...is because I don't have a real woman in my life.
je n'ai pas de femme réelle dans ma vie.
-You happy? -Yeah. That'll hold me for a while.
- Heureuse ? - Ça me va pour l'instant.
Howard, you did have a real woman.
Tu avais une femme réelle.
l was right there in the next room while you were clicking that troll's brains out.
J‘étais dans la chambre d'à côté quand tu cliquais ce troll.
Yeah, but we weren't, heh-- I mean, you and I never--
Oui mais nous... Toi et moi n‘avons jamais...
-Had sex? -Yeah.
- Fait l‘amour ? - Oui.
-Well, whose fault was that? -Complimentary nachos.
- A qui la faute ? - Nachos gratuits.
You enjoy.
Régalez-vous.
Never had sex? Wow.
Jamais fait l‘amour ?
What do you mean, whose fault was that?
Comment ça, à qui la faute ?
We could've been having sex, but you never made the move.
Tu n'as pas fait le premier pas.
I didn't think you wanted me to make the move.
J'ignorais que je devais le faire.
Howard, a girl doesn't go out with a man like you, with your looks...
Une fille ne sort pas avec un homme comme toi
...your fancy patter, and your tight hoochie pants...
avec un super baratin et des pantalons en velours
...if she's not expecting him to eventually make the move.
si elle ne veut pas qu'il fasse le premier pas.
-Really? -Really.
- Vraiment ? - Vraiment.
Son of a bitch.
Ca alors !
This is a little awkward...
C‘est bizarre
...but my manager says I can't actually give nachos away...
mais mon chef m‘a interdit de donner des nachos
...so just take that when you're ready.
donc tu me paieras ça quand tu seras prêt.
I mean, we had a really great talk.
On a eu une discussion.
We're gonna start seeing each other again.
On va recommencer à se voir.
Oh, congratulations.
Félicitations. Tu as cassé avec le troll ?
-Did Penny tell you about that? -No, Steve Patterson told me.
- Penny t'en a parlé ? - Non. Steve Patterson me l‘a dit.
The greasy old fat guy in Facilities Management?
Le gros mec dégoûtant du service Management ?
-Yeah. -How'd he know about it?
- Oui. - Comment le sait-il ?
He's Glissinda the Troll.
C‘est lui, Glissinda Ie Troll.
[INDIAN MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Désolé, mon pote. Le thermostat est de mon côté.
SHELDON: I'll turn off the music...
J‘éteindrai la musique quand cet oiseau aura foutu le camp.
RAJESH: Oh, too bad. Sheldon's pathologically afraid of birds.
Terrible ! La peur incontrôlée des oiseaux.
Hey, look, Sheldon. Birdie, birdie, birdie.
Regarde, Sheldon. Petit, petit, petit.
SHELDON: That's it. Prepare for marshmallow death.
Tu vas mourir à coups de guimauve.
RAJESH: Eat flaming Nerf!
Flammes affaiblissantes !
So, anyway....
C‘est une bonne nouvelle pour Bernadette et toi.
-l'm gonna take her to miniature golf. -Oh.
Je l‘amène au mini—golf.
I guess, for you guys, that's like regular golf.
Pour toi, c‘est comme du golf normal.
Shortjokes? Really? You're like a quarter of an inch taller than me.
Petite blague ? Tu es à peine plus grand que moi.
Yeah, and don't you forget it.
Et ne l'oublie pas.
-I had a good time. -Me too.
- J'ai passé une bonne soirée. - Moi aussi.
Kiss her good night.
Embrasse—la.
-All right, now a little tongue. -Hold on there.
- Maintenant, avec la langue. - Non.
We've only just rekindled the romance.
Ils viennentjuste de se rabibocher.
Let's not sully the moment with the exchange of saliva.
Ne salissons pas ce moment avec un échange de salive.
Don't listen to him. She wants it. Tongue.
Ne l'écoute pas. Elle en a envie. La langue.
See?
Tu vois ?
-Now make the move. -Mm-mm. Too soon.
- Maintenant, passe à l‘acte. - Trop tôt.
Trust me, she's ready. Make the move.
Elle est prête. Fais le premier pas.
No, no, no. A lady wants to be wooed...
Non. Une femme aime être charmée,
...courted slowly.
courtisée tout doucement.
How would you know?
Qu'est—ce que tu en sais ?
I read.
Je lis.
Listen to me, Howard. It's time. Make the move, now.
Écoute-moi, Howard. C‘est le moment. Vas-y.
-What are you doing? -You said-- Well, the move, remember?
- Que fais-tu ? - Je fais le premier pas.
Well, not now. We're starting a new relationship.
On commence une nouvelle relation.
-I need to get to know you again. -No, you don't. It's me.
- Je dois apprendre à te connaître. - Mais non. C‘est moi.
The lusty charmer with the fancy patter and the hoochie pants.
Le vigoureux charmeur au super baratin et aux pantalons en velours.
Be patient. We'll get there.
Sois patient. On vale faire.
Told you.
Je te l‘avais dit.
Oh, God, what is that smell?
C‘est quoi, cette odeur ?
SHELDON: Yes?
Oui ?
-What are you doing in there? -l'm making hydrogen sulfide...
- Que fais-tu ? - Je fais du sulfure d‘hydrogène
...and ammonia gas.
et de l‘ammoniac.
Just a little experiment in pest control.
Une expérience de désinsectisation.
RAJESH: It's not gonna work, dude. I grew up in India...
Ça ne marchera pas. J'ai grandi en Inde
...a subcontinent where cows walk in the street...
où les vaches marchent dans la rue
...and nobody has ever had a solid bowel movement.
et où tout le monde ala diarrhée.
SHELDON: Well, we'll just see how long you can hold out.
On verra combien de temps tu peux tenir.
We'll just see how your noxious gas fares...
Nous verrons si ton gaz rivalise
...against my cinnamon-apple-scented aromatherapy candles.
avec mes bougies parfumées àla pomme et à la cannelle.
Didn't you say you're making hydrogen sulfide gas?
Tu n'es pas en train de faire du gaz ?
-Yes. -lsn't that flammable?
- Si. - C‘est inflammable ?
SHELDON: Highly.
Hautement.
Oh, dear.
Mon Dieu.
This is not over.
Ce n‘est pas fini.
[English - us - an]
[French]